<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Love Your Wife</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>

    <string name="day1text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Loving your wife begins in your own heart and extends outward.  Today, write down 20 things about your wife that you are truly grateful for.  </string>
    <string name="day2text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Today, we remember to take the actions, and the feelings will follow.  Do one of the chores your wife normally does in a spirit of generosity.  Do not expect to be thanked.</string>
    <string name="day3text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Sit down with your wife and plan an easy date night together that works for both of you.  Set it in the calendar.  You can mark this challenge as complete once the day is set and you have put it in the calendar.  Write down the date planned and what you will be doing.</string>
    <string name="day4text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Has your wife ever said something about your physical appearance that she has wanted you to change, or has implied she would desire?  If not, ask.  Now that you are married, your body belongs to your wife too. Take an action to move one step closer to become your wife’s ideal husband.  What did you do?  </string>
    <string name="day5text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Your wife should know she comes first in your life, and one of the best ways to show her is by giving her your undivided attention.  Today, whenever your wife speaks to you, drop what you are doing, turn toward her, and truly listen, taking the time to hear out all that is on her mind.  How did it go?</string>
    <string name="day6text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Bring home a gift for your wife.  Wives love to know you are thinking about them when they are away, and that you are willing to spend hard earned dollars for them.  Flowers usually do the trick.  Unless she really hates flowers… then you get to be creative!  How did she respond?</string>
    <string name="day7text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Make time to go for a walk together. Phones stay at home.  Going for a walk is a great to get out of the house, enjoy the outdoors, and have time talking about whatever comes to mind.  Many couples do this on a regular basis.  How did it go? </string>
    <string name="day8text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Write down some of the things your wife does around the house that you really appreciate.  Get a post it note or piece of paper, choose one of those things, and write a note expressing your thanks.  Post it somewhere she will see it when she is about to do that chore.</string>
    <string name="day9text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020What is your wife’s favorite candy? Leave it for her to find on her pillow when she goes to bed. </string>
    <string name="day10text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Take time today to pray with your wife.  Ask her if there is anything you can pray about for her.  Do this out loud, in her presence.  If you are not religious, come up with your own challenge today and write down what you did.</string>
    <string name="day11text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020What is your wife’s favorite animal?  If you don’t know, ask her and write it down.  Send her 4 to 5 cute gifs or short videos of that animal throughout the day.  How did she respond? </string>
    <string name="day12text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Leave a message on your wife’s breakfast or lunch.  Share one of your favorite memories of a dinner date with her.</string>
    <string name="day13text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Go shopping with your wife and buy something for her. </string>
    <string name="day14text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Today, you get to take personal inventory.  How do you think you have been as a husband?  Write down 3 strengths and 3 weakness.  Choose one of those weaknesses.  Tell your wife that you know you have not been what you want to be in that particular area, and apologize if this has hurt her.  Tell her you will try to make improvements upon it in the future, and give her specific examples of what you plan to do to make that happen.</string>
    <string name="day15text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020It is important that your wife knows you speak well of her in front of others.  Today, publicly express gratitude for something about your wife in front of your family or friends.  Yes, Facebook counts too. </string>
    <string name="day16text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Take time to hold your wife’s hand or give your wife a hug today.  It is important that we show physical affection that is also non-sexual, so the woman knows we love them for more than just their body and what happens in bed.  Write down what you did, and how she responded.</string>
    <string name="day17text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Notice something she has mentioned that needs replacing around your home and do it without asking. </string>
    <string name="day18text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Is there something your wife has done that has hurt you?  Write it down here  Today, realize that no one is perfect. Forgive your wife in your heart, as you would want to be forgiven.  If you need to forgive her in person, do so and write about the response.  When finished, write \"Forgiven\".</string>
    <string name="day19text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020You can’t love your wife if you don’t love yourself, too.  Today, take time to take care of yourself.  Some ideas:  Take a nap, do some journaling, pray, workout, or do something that is refreshing and that gives you energy. The better you take care of yourself, the better you can take care of her.  Write down what you did and how it affected you.  </string>
    <string name="day20text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Plan a movie night, in or out.  Let her pick the movie. If she enjoys British mysteries, house hunting, or Rom Coms, deal with it. You’ll enjoy it, too. </string>
    <string name="day21text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020True love is sometimes about sacrificing something of yourself for the other person.  Your wife should be more important to you than anyone or anything, minus God himself.  Is there anything you need to give up to love your wife more?</string>
    <string name="day22text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Give your wife physical affection - let her know you would like to give her a back rub tonight so she can plan on making time for it.  Massage oil is a plus!</string>
    <string name="day23text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Write her a letter, telling her one of your favorite memories together and leave it in her wallet or journal- somewhere she may not notice it right away.</string>
    <string name="day24text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Sometimes loving someone else starts by loving yourself.   Take care of your personal appearance today.  She’ll appreciate your facial grooming, as well as hand and toenails.  Get a haircut, if it is time.  </string>
    <string name="day25text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Send her a text every hour (or periodically) and tell her something that reminds you of her. She’ll like to know you’re thinking of her throughout your day!</string>
    <string name="day26text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Write down some things you appreciate about your wife’s physical appearance.  Look her in the eye and compliment her on this.  </string>
    <string name="day27text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020One of the most important things we need to do in marriage is truly listen to eachother.  Today, check in with your wife.  How is she doing?  Really listen, asking questions, making sure you understand where she is coming from.  If she is distressed, ask if there is anything you can do to help.  How is she?</string>
    <string name="day28text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Plan and set a fancy date in the calendar. Something unusual that you wouldn’t usually do. Dress up.  Complete this challenge when the place and date are set. </string>
    <string name="day29text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Tell her you love her.</string>
    <string name="day30text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020This final challenge is difficult.  Find a time with your wife that you can set aside to talk face to face.  Ask your wife how she feels you have been treating her.  Ask her what you can do to make her feel more loved.  Ask her what you can do to be a better husband. Do not criticize, just listen.  Thank her for her honest feedbacks, and be willing to tell her that you are planning to make changes in your life on those issues.  Afterward, write down some of the major points here.  How can you practically address her concerns?</string>

    <string name="inspire1">\"I take thee to be my wedded wife, to have and to hold from this day forward, for better, for worse, for richer, for poorer, in sickness and in health, to love and to cherish, till death do us part, according to God\'s holy ordinance; and thereto I pledge thee my faith.\"
        \n\n — Traditional Wedding Vow</string>
    <string name="inspire2">\"Love is always bestowed as a gift -freely, willingly, and without expectation. We don’t love to be loved, we love to love.\"
\n\n — Leo Buscagalia</string>
    <string name="inspire3">\"To get the full value of joy you must have someone to divide it with.\"
 \n\n — Mark Twain</string>
    <string name="inspire4">\"Death cannot stop true love.  All it can do is delay it for a while.\"
        \n\n — Wesley, The Princess Bride</string>
    <string name="inspire5">\"My most brilliant achievement was my ability to persuade my wife to marry me.\"
 \n\n — Winston Churchill</string>
    <string name="inspire6">\"Husbands, love your wives, just as Christ loved the church and gave himself up for her.\"
 \n\n — Ephesians 5:25</string>
    <string name="inspire7">\"Two are better than one, \n
    because they have a good return for their labor:\n
        If either of them falls down,\n
    one can help the other up.\n
But pity anyone who falls\n
    and has no one to help them up.\n
Also, if two lie down together, they will keep warm.\n
    But how can one keep warm alone?\n
Though one may be overpowered,\n
    two can defend themselves.\n
A cord of three strands is not quickly broken.\"
    \n\n — Ephesians 4:9-12</string>
    <string name="inspire8">\"Whatever we do or suffer for a friend is pleasant, because love is the principal cause of pleasure.\"
 \n\n — Thomas Aquinas</string>

    <string name="inspire9">\"Darkness cannot drive out darkness; only light can do that. Hate cannot drive out hate; only love can do that.\"
 \n\n — Martin Luther King Jr.</string>
    <string name="inspire10">\"Honor her for all that her hands have done,  \n
                        and let her works bring her praise at the city gate.\"
        \n\n — Proverbs 31:31</string>
    <string name="inspire11">\"You come to love not by finding the perfect person, but by learning to see an imperfect person perfectly.\"
 \n\n — Sam Keen</string>
    <string name="inspire12">\"There are only two days in the year that nothing can be done. One is called Yesterday and the other is called Tomorrow.\"
 \n\n — Dalai Lama XIV</string>
    <string name="inspire13">\"Marriage is a workshop… where the husband works and the wife shops.\"
 \n\n — The Internet</string>
    <string name="inspire14">\"I destroy my enemy if I make him my friend.\"
 \n\n — Abraham Lincoln</string>
    <string name="inspire15">\"I pronounce you man and wife.  You may now change your facebook status.\"
        \n\n — Anonymous</string>
    <string name="inspire16">\"I am my beloved\'s, and my beloved is mine.\"
 \n\n — Song of Solomon 8:3</string>
   <string name="inspire17">\"I would rather share one lifetime with you than face all the ages of this world alone.\"
 \n\n — Arwen, The Fellowship of The Ring</string>
    <string name="inspire18">\"Be completely humble and gentle; be patient, bearing with one another in love.\"
 \n\n — Ephesians 4:2</string>
    <string name="inspire19">\"Love is a mighty pretty thing; but like all other delicious things, it is cloying; and when the first transports of the passion begins to subside, which it assuredly will do, and yield, oftentimes too late, to more sober reflections, it serves to evince, that love is too dainty a food to live upon alone, and ought not to be considered farther than as a necessary ingredient for that matrimonial happiness which results from a combination of causes.\"
 \n\n — George Washington</string>
    <string name="inspire20">\"Stay with me to-night; you must see me die. I have long had the taste of death on my tongue, I smell death, and who will stand by my Constanze, if you do not stay?\"
 \n\n — Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart</string>
    <string name="inspire21">\"It takes courage to love, but pain through love is the purifying fire which those who love generously know. We all know people who are so much afraid of pain that they shut themselves up like clams in a shell and, giving out nothing, receive nothing and therefore shrink until life is a mere living death.\"
 \n\n — Eleanor Roosevelt</string>
    <string name="inspire22">\"I believe myself that romantic love is the source of the most intense delights that life has to offer. In the relation of a man and woman who love each other with passion and imagination and tenderness, there is something of inestimable value, to be ignorant of which is a great misfortune to any human being.\"
        \n\n — Bertrand Russell</string>
    <string name="inspire23">\"Love is a fruit in season at all times, and within reach of every hand. Anyone may gather it and no limit is set. Everyone can reach this love through meditation, spirit of prayer, and sacrifice, by an intense inner life.\"
 \n\n — Mother Theresa</string>
    <string name="inspire24">"Love your neighbor as you love yourself."
     \n\n — Jesus, Matthew 22:39</string>
    <string name="inspire25">\"The Caladrius is a bird of which it is related that, when it is carried into the presence of a sick person, if the sick man is going to die, the bird turns away its head and never looks at him; but if the sick man is to be saved the bird never loses sight of him but is the cause of curing him of all his sickness. Like unto this is the love of virtue. It never looks at any vile or base thing, but rather clings always to pure and virtuous things and takes up its abode in a noble heart; as the birds do in green woods on flowery branches. And this Love shows itself more in adversity than in prosperity; as light does, which shines most where the place is darkest.\"
 \n\n — Leonardo Davinci</string>
    <string name="inspire26">\"Marriage is when a man looses his bachelors degree and a woman gets her masters degree.\"
     \n   \n — Rama Kochar</string>
    <string name="inspire27">\"If I speak in the tongues of men or of angels, but do not have love, I am only a resounding gong or a clanging cymbal. If I have the gift of prophecy and can fathom all mysteries and all knowledge, and if I have a faith that can move mountains, but do not have love, I am nothing. If I give all I possess to the poor and give over my body to hardship that I may boast, but do not have love, I gain nothing.\"
 \n\n — 1 Cor. 13:1-3</string>
    <string name="inspire28">\"But love your enemies, do good to them, and lend to them without expecting to get anything back. Then your reward will be great, and you will be children of the Most High, because he is kind to the ungrateful and wicked.\"
        \n\n — Jesus, Luke 6:35</string>
    <string name="inspire29">\"My very dear Sarah: &#8230;[ ]&#8230; The memories of the blissful moments I have spent with you come creeping over me, and I feel most gratified to God and to you that I have enjoyed them for so long. And hard it is for me to give them up and burn to ashes the hopes of future years, when, God willing, we might still have lived and loved together, and seen our sons grown up to honorable manhood, around us. I have, I know, but few and small claims upon Divine Providence, but something whispers to me — perhaps it is the wafted prayer of my little Edgar, that I shall return to my loved ones unharmed. If I do not my dear Sarah, never forget how much I love you, and when my last breath escapes me on the battle field, it will whisper your name. Forgive my many faults and the many pains I have caused you. How thoughtless and foolish I have often times been! How gladly would I wash out with my tears every little spot upon your happiness &#8230;\"
        \n\n — Sullivan Ballou</string>
    <string name="inspire30">\"Greater love has no one than this, that someone lay down his life for his friends.\"
 \n\n — Jesus, John 15:13</string>

    <string name="invitation_title">LoveYourWife Invitation</string>
    <string name="invitation_message">Hi, I\'ve been using this app called "Love Your Wife". It can help improve you marriage.\u0020</string>
    <string name="invitation_deep_link">google.com</string>
    <string name="invitation_cta">Click here to open</string>

    <string name="title_activity_challenge_complete">Challenge Complete</string>
    <string name="Completed30Days">You have Completed the 30 day Challenge to Love Your Wife!</string>
    <string name="RecommendMessage">Hi, I want to recommend the App Love Your Wife. It can help to improve your relationship with your wife.\u0020</string>
    <string name="RecommendSubject">Love Your Wife</string>
    <string name="RecommendMessageHTML"><![CDATA[<p>Hi!  I\'ve been using this app called Love Your Wife, and wanted to recommend it to you. It has great ideas to improve your marriage and love your wife better. Click on this link to check it out.]]></string>
    <string name="RecommendToFriendTitle">Recommend Love Your Wife to a friend</string>
    <string name="Invitation_Error">Error creating invitation link.  Are you connected to the internet?</string>
    <string name="ProblemLoadingBillingClient">Problem Loading the Billing Client through Google.</string>
    <string name="BillingDisconnected">Love Your Wife Billing Service disconnected.</string>
    <string name="BillingDisconnectStartService">Billing is disconnected, called startServiceconnection again</string>
    <string name="BillingNotSupported">Google Play billing is not supported on this device.</string>
    <string name="Day">Day</string>
    <string name="CompleteChallengeOn">Complete the challenge on day</string>
    <string name="SpaceToUnlock">to unlock.</string>
    <string name="CompleteChallengeForTrophy">You must complete a challenge to obtain a trophy.</string>
    <string name="completed">Completed!</string>
    <string name="error_completing_dialog_message">Check your internet connection. Try again?</string>
    <string name="error_completing_dialog_title">Error Completing Challenge</string>
    <string name="try_again">Try again</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
</resources>
