<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Love Your Wife</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>

    <string name="day1text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Loving your wife begins in your own heart and extends outward.  Today, write down 20 things about your wife that you are truly grateful for.  </string>
    <string name="day2text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Today, we remember to take the actions, and the feelings will follow.  Do one of the chores your wife normally does in a spirit of generosity.  Do not expect to be thanked.</string>
    <string name="day3text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Sit down with your wife and plan an easy date night together that works for both of you.  Set it in the calendar.  You can mark this challenge as complete once the day is set and you have put it in the calendar.  Write down the date planned and what you will be doing.</string>
    <string name="day4text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Has your wife ever said something about your physical appearance that she has wanted you to change, or has implied she would desire?  If not, ask.  Now that you are married, your body belongs to your wife too. Take an action to move one step closer to become your wife’s ideal husband.  What did you do?  </string>
    <string name="day5text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020It is important that your wife knows she comes first in your life, and one of the best ways to do this is by giving her your undivided attention.  Today, whenever your wife speaks to you, drop what you are doing, turn toward her, and truly listen, taking the time to hear out all that is on her mind.  How did it go?</string>
    <string name="day6text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Bring home a gift for your wife.  Wives love to know you are thinking about them when they are away, and that you are willing to spend hard earned dollars for them.  Flowers usually do the trick.  Unless she really hates flowers… then you get to be creative!  How did she respond?</string>
    <string name="day7text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Make time to go for a walk together. Phones stay at home.  Going for a walk is a great to get out of the house, enjoy the outdoors, and have time talking about whatever comes to mind.  Many couples do this on a regular basis.  How did it go? </string>
    <string name="day8text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Write down some of the things your wife does around the house that you really appreciate.  Get a post it note or piece of paper, choose one of those things, and write a note expressing your thanks.  Post it somewhere she will see it when she is about to do that chore.</string>
    <string name="day9text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020What is your wife’s favorite candy? Leave it for her to find on her pillow when she goes to bed. </string>
    <string name="day10text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020What is your wife’s favorite animal?  If you don’t know, ask her and write it down.  Send her 4 to 5 cute gifs or short videos of that animal throughout the day.  How did she respond? </string>
    <string name="day11text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Take time today to pray with your wife.  Ask her if there is anything you can pray about for her.  Do this out loud, in her presence.  If you are not religious, come up with your own challenge today and write down what you did.</string>
    <string name="day12text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Leave a message on your wife’s breakfast or lunch.  Share one of your favorite memories of a dinner date with her.</string>
    <string name="day13text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Go shopping with your wife and buy something for her. </string>
    <string name="day14text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Today, you get to take personal inventory.  How do you think you have been as a husband?  Write down 3 strengths and 3 weakness.  Choose one of those weaknesses.  Tell your wife that you know you have not been what you want to be in that particular area, and apologize if this has hurt her.  Tell her you will try to make improvements upon it in the future, and give her specific examples of what you plan to do to make that happen.</string>
    <string name="day15text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020It is important that your wife knows you speak well of her in front of others.  Today, publicly express gratitude for something about your wife in front of your family or friends.  Yes, Facebook counts too. </string>
    <string name="day16text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Take time to hold your wife’s hand or give your wife a hug today.  It is important that we show physical affection that is also non-sexual, so the woman knows we love them for more than just their body and what happens in bed.  Write down what you did, and how she responded.</string>
    <string name="day17text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Notice something she has mentioned that needs replacing around your home and do it without asking. </string>
    <string name="day18text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Send her an ecard. It can be a free one. The message you write is the one that counts.</string>
    <string name="day19text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020You can’t love your wife if you don’t love yourself, too.  Today, take time to take care of yourself.  Some ideas:  Take a nap, do some journaling, pray, workout, or do something that is refreshing and that gives you energy. The better you take care of yourself, the better you can take care of her.  Write down what you did and how it affected you.  </string>
    <string name="day20text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Plan a movie night, in or out.  Let her pick the movie. If she enjoys British mysteries, house hunting, or Rom Coms, deal with it. You’ll enjoy it, too. </string>
    <string name="day21text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020True love is sometimes about sacrificing something of yourself for the other person.  Your wife should be more important to you than anyone or anything, minus God himself.  Is there anything you need to give up to love your wife more?</string>
    <string name="day22text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Give your wife physical affection - let her know you would like to give her a back rub tonight so she can plan on making time for it.  Massage oil is a plus!</string>
    <string name="day23text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Write her a letter, telling her one of your favorite memories together and leave it in her wallet or journal- somewhere she may not notice it right away.</string>
    <string name="day24text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Sometimes loving someone else starts by loving yourself.   Take care of your personal appearance today.  She’ll appreciate your facial grooming, as well as hand and toenails.  Get a haircut, if it is time.  </string>
    <string name="day25text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Send her a text every hour (or periodically) and tell her something that reminds you of her. She’ll like to know you’re thinking of her throughout your day!</string>
    <string name="day26text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Write down some things you appreciate about your wife’s physical appearance.  Look her in the eye and compliment her on this.  </string>
    <string name="day27text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020One of the most important things we need to do in marriage is truly listen to eachother.  Today, check in with your wife.  How is she doing?  Really listen, asking questions, making sure you understand where she is coming from.  If she is distressed, ask if there is anything you can do to help.  How is she?</string>
    <string name="day28text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Plan and set a fancy date in the calendar. Something unusual that you wouldn’t usually do. Dress up.  Complete this challenge when the place and date are set. </string>
    <string name="day29text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Tell her you love her.</string>
    <string name="day30text">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020This final challenge is difficult.  Find a time with your wife that you can set aside to talk face to face.  Ask your wife how she feels you have been treating her.  Ask her what you can do to make her feel more loved.  Ask her what you can do to be a better husband. Do not criticize, just listen.  Thank her for her honest feedbacks, and be willing to tell her that you are planning to make changes in your life on those issues.  Afterward, write down some of the major points here.  How can you practically address her concerns?</string>

    <string name="inspire1">day 1 inspiration.</string>
    <string name="inspire18">18 inspire!!!!</string>

    <string name="invitation_title">LoveYourWife Invitation</string>
    <string name="invitation_message">Hi, I\'ve been using this app called "LoveYourWife", and I recommend you check it out.</string>
    <string name="invitation_deep_link">google.com</string>
    <string name="invitation_cta">Click here to open</string>


    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_challenge_complete">Challenge Complete</string>
</resources>
